{
    "subject": "resource/Epoxies",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Epoxies' hometown is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8241106867790222,
            "question": "Is Epoxies originally from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114432096481323,
            "question": "What country is Epoxies' hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7512922883033752,
            "question": "In what part of the US might Epoxies live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7169674634933472,
            "question": "Are there any famous people or landmarks associated with Epoxies' hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.602121114730835,
            "question": "What kind of life might someone lead in Epoxies' hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5932341814041138,
            "question": "Where is Epoxies from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.57538241147995,
            "question": "Do you have any other information about Epoxies besides their hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49461784958839417,
            "question": "What can you infer about Epoxies' cultural background based on their hometown?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41870278120040894,
            "question": "How might knowing Epoxies' hometown influence your understanding of them?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3187538981437683,
            "question": "Could Epoxies be from a different place now?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Epoxies' hometown is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9055_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might knowing Epoxies' hometown influence your understanding of them?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9055_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can you infer about Epoxies' cultural background based on their hometown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9055_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have any other information about Epoxies besides their hometown?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9055_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9055_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that epoxies originated in Germany/Switzerland and later became popular in the United States.  It does not claim that their \"hometown\" is the United States. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"Epoxies' hometown is United States\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while some epoxies are mentioned to be made in the United States, it does not imply that all epoxies or their \"hometown\" is the United States. In fact, one of the documents mentions that many epoxy products out there aren't manufactured here in the United States, and are instead manufactured overseas, such as in China."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that many epoxy products are manufactured overseas, but they also highlight the importance of buying epoxy products made in the United States to support local economies and ensure higher quality. Specifically, one document mentions KSRESIN's commitment to producing their epoxy resin products proudly in the United States with a 90-day guarantee. This supports the statement that epoxies' hometown is the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Epoxies were initially developed in Germany and Switzerland, not the United States.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states that epoxy resin originated in Germany/Switzerland and later became an American product through companies like Ciba and Huntsman Corporation.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the origin of epoxies, specifically bisphenol-A-based epoxy resins, predates the United States' involvement in their production and development, with early reports and patents dating back to Germany (1934) and Switzerland (1943).",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}